// JSON object to hold all our questions and answers - kl
    // add some questions here
    var questions = {
        "one": {
            "question": "What does js stand for?",
            "answerOne":"jQuery Script",
            "answerTwo":"Java Serialized",
            "answerThree":"JSONScript",
            "answerFour":"JavaScript",
            "correctAnswer":"answerFour"
        },
         "two": {
             "question":"How do you print a message to the console?",
             "answerOne":"Logger.log();",
             "answerTwo":"console.log();",
             "answerThree":"console.log[];",
             "answerFour":"Console.log();",
             "correctAnswer":"answerTwo"
         },
        // "three": {
        //     "question":"How do you push a value to an array?",
        //     "answerOne":"array.push(value);",
        //     "answerTwo":"push[array,value];",
        //     "answerThree":"array_push(array,value);",
        //     "answerFour":"array.push[value];",
        //     "correctAnswer":"answerOne"
        // },
        // "four": {
        //     "question":"How do you print a message to the console?",
        //     "answerOne":"Logger.log()",
        //     "answerTwo":"console.log()",
        //     "answerThree":"console.log[]",
        //     "answerFour":"Console.log()",
        //     "correctAnswer":"answerTwo"
        // },
        // "five": {
        //     "question":"How do you print a message to the console?",
        //     "answerOne":"Logger.log()",
        //     "answerTwo":"console.log()",
        //     "answerThree":"console.log[]",
        //     "answerFour":"Console.log()",
        //     "correctAnswer":"answerTwo"
        // },
        // "six": {
        //     "question":"How do you push a value to an array?",
        //     "answerOne":"array.push(value);",
        //     "answerTwo":"push[array,value];",
        //     "answerThree":"array_push(array,value);",
        //     "answerFour":"array.push[value];",
        //     "correctAnswer":"answerOne"
        // },
        // "seven": {
        //     "question":"How do you print a message to the console?",
        //     "answerOne":"Logger.log()",
        //     "answerTwo":"console.log()",
        //     "answerThree":"console.log[]",
        //     "answerFour":"Console.log()",
        //     "correctAnswer":"answerTwo"
        // },
        // "eight": {
        //     "question": "What does js stand for?",
        //     "answerOne":"jQuery Script",
        //     "answerTwo":"Java Serialized",
        //     "answerThree":"JSONScript",
        //     "answerFour":"JavaScript",
        //     "correctAnswer":"answerFour"
        // },
        // "nine": {
        //     "question":"How do you print a message to the console?",
        //     "answerOne":"Logger.log()",
        //     "answerTwo":"console.log()",
        //     "answerThree":"console.log[]",
        //     "answerFour":"Console.log()",
        //     "correctAnswer":"answerTwo"
        // },
        // "ten": {
        //     "question":"How do you print a message to the console?",
        //     "answerOne":"Logger.log()",
        //     "answerTwo":"console.log()",
        //     "answerThree":"console.log[]",
        //     "answerFour":"Console.log()",
        //     "correctAnswer":"answerTwo"
        // }
    }